{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "1. kérdés",
		            "content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
				{
					"question" : "2. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct" : 1
				},
				{
					"question" : "3. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct" : 2
				},
				{
					"question": "4. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 3
				},
				{
					"question": "5. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 0
				},
				{
					"question" : "6. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct" : 1
				},
				{
					"question": "7. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 2
				},
				{
					"question": "8. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 1
				},
				{
					"question": "9. kérdés",
				    "content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 1
				},
				{
					"question": "10. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 3
				},
				{
					"question" : "11. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct" : 0
				},
				{
					"question": "12. kérdés",
				    "content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 1
				},
				{
					"question": "13. kérdés",
				    "content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 0
				},
				{
					"question": "14. kérdés",
					"content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 2
				},
				{
					"question": "15. kérdés",
				    "content" : [
		                "Válasz A",
		                "Válasz B",
		                "Válasz C",
		                "Válasz D"
		            ],
					"correct": 3
				}
		    ]
		}
	]
}